

ABOUT ME

IT professional with seven years of experience in Project Management, Business Analysis, and testing. I am currently attending Capella University for a Ph.D. in Information Assurance and Cybersecurity. I have obtained multiple certifications including ITIL Foundations, CompTIA A+, Network+, Security+, SSCP, Web Security Professional, and Certified Ethical Hacker. My strengths include hard working, problem solving, critical and strategic thinking, working well in team and individual environments.

CONTACT

PHONE:

317-995-1715

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mac-wells-6087b375/

EMAIL:

mac.g.wells@gmail.com

Address:

176 Huntingdon Dr Leesburg, GA, 31763

SKILLS

- Security Standard Operating Procedure Writing
- Researching
- Metasploit
- Nessus
- SQL
- Nmap
- Documentation
- Requirement gathering

MAC WELLS

BUSINESS ANALYST

EDUCATION

Western Governors University

February 2018 – January 2020 Bachelor of Science - Cybersecurity and Information Assurance

March 2020 – February 2021 Master of Science – Cybersecurity and Information Assurance

Capella University

April 2021 - Present

Ph.D. Information Technology – Information Assurance and Cybersecurity

WORK EXPERIENCE

VetsEZ- Business Analyst

August 2021 - Current

Functional analyst and technical analyst. Assist with migration projects and continuous improvement on a product in sustainment. Work with stakeholders and leadership to prioritize work and run daily, weekly, and monthly reporting. Assist with obtaining security approvals for products and writing documentation needed for security approvals. Writing security standard operating procedures and retrieving security artifacts.

CGI Federal – Senior Consultant

June 2020 - Current

My primary role was a tester/helpdesk associate. Answer helpdesk calls multiple days a week along with answering helpdesk emails daily. Calls and emails include but are not limited to, verification of document fulfillment meeting government standards, access requests, verifying security training completion, and reactivation request fulfillment. Ensuring access controls for users are properly implemented including least privilege principal. Along with testing new functionality and bug fixes. Leading 508 compliance testing and creating standard operating procedures for 508 standards. Ensuring that the CIA triad is followed. Testing for security implementation. This includes identity and access management, according to government standards, this is role and classification based, assist in security assessments, and assist in regression testing.

Xome Valuations - Business Systems Analyst

November 2013 – June 2020

Functional and Technical analyst with a focus on integrations with proprietary systems. Established multiple workflows for government processes within Xome Valuations. Sole Business Analyst for integrations with experience on multi-month projects. Working with both internal and external stakeholders to elicit requirements, provide updates, and present information/project results. Assist QA teams with testing. Assist development team with code reviews. Assist the business with client calls. Elicit requirements from both clients and business stakeholders. Also assisted with ensuring PII was handled appropriately within the

application, ensure PCI compliance was established within the application, ensured that principle of least privilege and separation of duties was established using a role-based access management process, and ensure strong password strength requirement were implemented. Assist in implementing security thought process and implementation within development. Discuss and write requirements that included security requirements.

Xome Valuations (formerly StreetLinks Lender Solutions) - Escalations Processing Trainer/Coach

November 2012 – December 2013

Teach, train, and Mentored Escalation Associates to do all they could for every file. Also trained new associates coming into the department about the position and different mind frame for the position.

Xome Valuations (formerly StreetLinks Lender Solutions) - Delivery Investigations Team Lead

December 2011 - November 2012

I created this team to help with issues clients may face with the Uniform Collateral Data Portal. This included reviewing XML's to make sure that they were correct and matched what was in the appraisals and to know all the guidelines set forth by Freddy and Fannie. I also took inbound calls to assist clients with the process of connect with us for UCDP and resolving their issues they encountered for UCDP.

CERTIFICATIONS

- ITIL Foundation Certificate in IT Service Management (License Number: GR750417823MW)
- CompTIA A+ ce (Credential ID: PXECS5Q3RH41Q9CJ)
- CompTIA Network+ ce (Credential ID: FQ5VNKSEZLE4Q353)
- CompTIA Project+ (Credential ID: 1TJ2ZJHEZPQEQ4CG)
- CompTIA Security+ (Credential ID: MJ8V45LMQPFQQHWN)
- CompTIA IT Operations Specialist (CIOS)
- CompTIA Secure Infrastructure Specialist (CSIS)
- CIW Web Security Professional (Credential ID: 873480)
- (ISC)² SSCP (Credential ID: 754807)
- EC-Council Certified Ethical Hacker (Credential ID: ECC7905418263)
- EC-Council Certified Incident Handler v2

(Credential ID: ECC7251064398)